{"id":"2017_17","name":"Romans2017_17","memoryVerse":"“What if he did this to make the riches of his glory known to the objects of his mercy, whom he prepared in advance for glory – even us, whom he also called, not only from the Jews but also from the Gentiles?” – Romans 9:23-24 ","dayQuestions":{"one":{"title":"FIRST DAY: Read the notes with references.","questions":[{"id":"2017_17_1","questionText":"1. What was meaningful to you in the lecture?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_17_2","questionText":"2. What help did you receive from the notes?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"two":{"title":"SECOND DAY: Read Romans 9:30-33.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"9:30-33"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_17_3","questionText":"3. What was the difference in the way the Gentiles and Israel approached righteousness? What were the results?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_17_4","questionText":"4. How is daily pursuing righteous behavior different from striving for righteous standing? What role does faith play?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_17_5","questionText":"5. Who is “the stumbling stone”? What about “the stumbling stone” causes people to stumble or fall?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"three":{"title":"THIRD DAY: Read Romans 10:1-4.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"10:1-4"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_17_6","questionText":"6. Why would Paul so strongly desire the Israelites be saved? How has God called you to pray for and minister tothose you desire to be saved?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_17_7","questionText":"7. What knowledge did the Israelites lack that caused their zeal to be misdirected? What does zealous behaviorwithout true knowledge of Jesus look like in today’s world? (Focus on behaviors without naming groups.)","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_17_8","questionText":"8. Explain Romans 10:4 in your own words. (You may want to read additional Bible translations to help you.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"10:4"}]}]},"four":{"title":"FOURTH DAY: Read Romans 10:5-9.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"10:5-9"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_17_9","questionText":"9. What conclusions does Paul make in light of these verses? (Note: Romans 10:5-7 can be interpreted in  various ways.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"10:5-7"}]},{"id":"2017_17_10","questionText":"10. What must a person do to be saved? ","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_17_11","questionText":"11. How would you take each phrase of verse 9 and explain its meaning and importance to an unbeliever?  ","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"five":{"title":"FIFTH DAY: Read Romans 10:10-13","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"10:10-13"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_17_12","questionText":"12. Share different aspects of the word “heart” from the following references: Matthew 6:21; 12:34; Romans 1:21-22; Galatians 4:6. As you meditate on these verses, what is God showing you about your heart? ","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Matthew","verse":"6:21"},{"book":"Matthew","verse":"12:34"},{"book":"Romans","verse":"1:21-22"},{"book":"Galatians","verse":"4:6"}]},{"id":"2017_17_13","questionText":"13. How does verse 13 relate to and clarify verse 11? According to these verses, to whom is salvation available?  ","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_17_14","questionText":"14. When did you (or will you) call on the name of the Lord for salvation?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"six":{"title":"SIXTH DAY: Review Romans 9:30-10:13.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"9:30-10:13"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_17_15","questionText":"15. What have you learned about God in this week’s study? How may your group pray for you as you make this truth a part of your life?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_17_16","questionText":"16. Homiletics for discussion and administrative leaders: Romans 9:30-10:13","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"9:30-10:13"}]}]}}}